https://www.ealing.gov.uk/info/201045/data_protection/1420/privacy_statement

Essential maintenance: Jobs
Jobs search and applications will be unavailable from 6pm, Friday 9 October until 9am, Monday 12 October for maintenance work. Sorry for any inconvenience caused.
COVID-19 updates
Close
Privacy notice
Home
Council and local decisions
Data protection
Privacy notice
Introduction
This privacy notice provides information about the types of personal data that we may collect about you when you contact us. It also explains what we will do with that data and how we will keep it safe.
The information in this privacy notice is correct as at 19 February 2019.
Personal information can be anything that identifies and relates to a living person. This can include information that when put together with other information can then identify a person. For example, this could be your name and contact details.
Ealing Council is the data controller for the personal data we collect. We are registered with the Information Commissioners Office and our registration number is Z5696801.
Data protection officer
The council has a data protection officer who has been notified to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).
The responsibilities of the data protection officer are:
to advise us on how to comply with our data protection obligations and an individual’s data rights
helps us monitor how we comply with our obligations and your rights, and
is our contact for the ICO.
You can contact them about your concerns at dataprotection@ealing.gov.uk or by writing to:
Data protection officer
Ealing Council
Perceval House
14-16 Uxbridge Road
3rd Floor NE
Ealing W5 2HL
Links
Please note that this privacy statement does not cover links to other websites.
Notification of changes
As Ealing Council creates new online services this may generate a need to amend this privacy statement. If substantial changes are made, the council will highlight such changes on the home page of the website.
Future developments
If our information changes at any time in the future Ealing Council will post the policy changes on this page.
Pages in Privacy notice
You are here: Introduction
Why do we process personal information?
What we do with personal information
What are our legal basis for processing personal data?
What personal data do we collect and for how long
Who do we share personal data with?
Cookies and information collected to improve our website
Departmental privacy notices
What are your individual rights over your personal data?
Coronavirus (COVID-19) privacy notice
NHS Test and Trace - recording customer details: How we use your information
Next page
Related Pages:
Business Services Group, Perceval House 3.SE, 14-16 Uxbridge Road, London W5 2HL
Handcrafted by Spacecraft,
Powered by Jadu Continuum.
